A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Correspondence, 1997-2006 [bulk 2001-2005]
  - Health and Human Resources: General, 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Health and Human Resources: General, 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Health and Human Resources: Review of Medicaid, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Health Benefits, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Health Insurance Flexibility and Accountability (HIFA), 2002-2004 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Health Savings Accounts, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Health Wagon, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Healthy Virginians Education for a Lifetime Standards of Acceditation, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Heinz Family Philanthropies, 2002-2003 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - HHR Board Nominees, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - HHR Emergency Response, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - REVIEW: HHR Emergency Response, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - HHR Persons Served - Budget, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - HJR 159 - JLARC, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Home Instead Senior Care, undated, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Home Instead Senior Care, undated, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Hospice / Elderly - Medicaid / Virginia Association of Health Plans, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Hospice Care for Children, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Hospital Focus Group, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Hot Button Topics [Birth Control], 2002 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - House Bill 25, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Human Resources, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Hurricane Katrina Response, 2005 [1] (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Hurricane Katrina Response, 2005 [2] (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Hurricane Katrina Response - Pickett, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Improve Business Productivity Through Effective Automation: Goal Three: Strategic Plan. Virginia Social Services System, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Information Technology, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Information Technology Investment Board: IT Project Review Committee, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Inspector General Findings, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Interagency Civil Admissions Advisory Council, 2003-2005 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Interagency Civital Admissions Advisory Council, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Inter-Secretary Agreement, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Invitations (Regrets), 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Invitations (Regrets), 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Invitations (Regrets), 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Invitations (Regrets), 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Invitations (Regrets), 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Invitations: 2004-2005, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Invitations: 2004-2005, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Invitations: 2004-2005, 2004-2005 [1], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Invitations: 2004-2005, 2004-2005 [1], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Invitations: 2004-2005, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Invitations: 2004-2005, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Issue Papers, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - IV-E Revenue Maximizing Issues, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - James Madison University, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - JLARC Request, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - John Millikea - DMAS and CSE, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 2002-2004 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Journal Articles, 2000-2003 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Journal: Health Affairs, v. 24 n. 2, March/April 2005, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - REVIEW: Kaufman v. Virginia, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Kessler, Keith, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Kid Safe Virginia, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Land Sale - Eastern State Hospital, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Leasing State Facility for Kids (Spanos), 2002 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Legal Council for DMHMRSAS, 2003 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Legal Issues, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Legislative, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Licensing, undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Long-Term Care and Prevention Services 2002 Program Report (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Long-Term Care Insurance, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Long-Term Care - OYOF, 2000-2005 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Managed Care, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Managed Care Reports, 2000-2004 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - March of Dimes (Virginia Prematurity Task Force), 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Martinsville Health and Dental Clinic Final Report, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Martinsville Health Fair, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - REVIEW: Mass Fatality Management Task Force, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - REVIEW: Mass Fatality Management Task Force, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Medical Facilities of America, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Medicaid/CSA Issues, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Medicare Modernization Act of 2003, 2003-2005 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Medicare Part D - Implications for Virginia, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Mental Health Mental Retardation Restructuring, 2001-2004, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Mental Health Mental Retardation Restructuring, 2001-2004, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Mental Health Mental Retardation Restructuring, 2001-2004, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Mental Health, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Mental Health, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Methadone, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - MHMR "Capacity", 2003 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Mission of Mercy Project, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Detailed Employee Report, 2001-2004 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - MR Waiver and Other Implementation Items After 2004 Session, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - REVIEW: National Capital Region Summit on Homeland Security, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - National Diabetic Pharmacies, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - National Governors Association, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - National Governors Association, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - National Governors Association (Special Projects), 2003 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - National Policy Academy on Co-Occuring Mental and Substance Abuse Disorders II: Pre Academy Site Visit, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - National Public Service Award, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - National Voter Registration Act, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - New CSA Data Elements, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - New School for Deaf and Blind (Consolidated), 2004 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Next Steps for CPMT Meetings, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - No Child Left Behind, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Non-Mandated CSA Kids/Initiatives, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Non-Mandated Funds in DMHMR, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Northern Virginia CPMT Roundtable, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Northern Virginia Family Service (NVFS), 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Norton Relay Center, 2002-2003 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Notes: Moving, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - REVEW: Notes: Moving, 2005 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Nursing Advisory Council, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Nursing, 2001-2005 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - OCS Staffing / Training, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Office of the Inspector General, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Oil and Hazardous Materials Emergency Response Plan, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Olmstead Initiative: Community Implementation Team, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - REVIEW: Olmstead-Related Law Suits, 2002 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - One Health, Inc., 2004-2005 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - One Virginia, One Future, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - One Virginia, One Future: Governor Warner's Economic Development Strategic Plan - Steering Committee Materials, 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - One Virginia, One Future: Governor Warner's Economic Development Strategic Plan - Steering Committee Materials, 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Organ Donation, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Originals for Subpoena - from NLR's Inbox, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Originals for Subpoena - from NLR's Inbox, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Originals for Subpoena - from NLR's Inbox, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Originals from Inventory II - Hunton and Williams FOIA, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Originals from Inventory II - Hunton and Williams FOIA, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Originals from Inventory II - Hunton and Williams FOIA, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Our Health, undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Own Your Future, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Own Your Future Virginia, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Partnership for Achieving Successful Schools (PASS), 2003 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Personnel, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - PharmAssist: A Best Practices Conference about Medication Assistance Programs for the Uninsured, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Piedmont Access to Health Services, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Planned Parenthood, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Poison Control, 2002-2004 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Portfolio: Virginia Workforce Council, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Private Collection Agencies, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Proclamations, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Projects, 2001-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Projects, 2001-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Proposal for an Interdepartmental Model of Regulation for Assisted Living Facilities, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Protecting Access to Healthcare (PATH), 2002 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Public Private Proposal, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Public-Private Partnerships in the Campaign ato Eliminate Health Discrepancies, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Put Virginia First Transition Committee, 2001, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Put Virginia First Transition Committee, 2001, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Put Virginia First: Executive Leadership Workshop of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Reach Out and Read, undated (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Records Retention, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Reinvestment, Initiative, undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Report on Housing Opportunities for Persons with Disabilities in Virginia, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance for the Quarter Ended 31 Mar 2005, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Report on the Implementation of 2005 Legislation for Assisted Living Facilities, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Report to the General Assembly, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Report: Draft Proposal for Comprehensive Alzheimer's Disease Center, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Report: Systemic Review of the Training Centers, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Request for Proposals (RFP) for Children's Advocacy Centers, 2005-2006, Item 298, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Restructuring, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Revenue Maximization, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Richmond Appeal (CSA), 2004 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Richmond Demographics, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Richmond Partnership for Children, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Rose Memorial - Senator Potts, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Rural Obstetrical Care - Executive Directive 2, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Rural Obstetrical Services Workgroup, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Rural PACE, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - SA/MH Treatment in Jails, 2001-2002 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Safety Nets, 2002-2004 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Satellite Office Sites, 2002, fo. 1 fo 2 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Satellite Office Sites, 2002, fo. 2 fo 2 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - SB 892, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Scheduling, 2002-2004 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - SEC Meeting, 30 June, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - REVIEW: Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: Secure Virginia, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Secure Virginia Panel, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - REVIEW: Secure Virginia Panel, 2003-2005 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Secure Virginia Panel: Domestic Preparedness, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Secure Virginia Panel: Public Health Briefing, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Security Alerts, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Security Assessment Supplement, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Septic Systems Case, 2001-2002 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Sexually Transmitted Diseases (STD) Prevention Efforts, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Sexually Violent Predators, 2001-2003, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Sexually Violent Predators, 2001-2003, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Sexually Violent Predators, 2001-2003, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Sexually Violent Predators, 2001-2003 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Sexually Violent Predators - Civil Commitment - MHMR, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - REVIEW: Sidoti, Mary Jane, 2001-2002 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Small, Women and Minority Business Report, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Smoking Cessation Resources, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Speeches: Aging, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Speeches: Aging, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Speeches: Aging, 2002-2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Speeches: Health, 2002-2004, fo. 1 fo 5 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Speeches: Health, 2002-2004, fo. 2 fo 5 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Speeches: Health, 2002-2004, fo. 3 fo 5 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Speeches: Health, 2002-2004, fo. 4 fo 5 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Speeches: Health, 2002-2004, fo. 5 fo 5 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Speeches: Other, 2002-2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Speeches: Other, 2002-2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Speeches: Social Services, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - State Coverage Initiative (SCI) Grant, 2002-2004, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - State Coverage Initiative (SCI) Grant, 2002-2004, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - State Coverage Initiative (SCI) Grant, 2002-2004, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - State Executive Council (SEC): Strategic Planning, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Statement of Economic Interest, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - REVIEW: Statewide Agency Radio System (STARS), 2003-2005 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Statewide Autism Council, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Statewide Contracts - CSA Workshop, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Status Reports on Redistricting, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Strategic Planning, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Subject File, 2002-2004 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - REVIEW: Subject File, 2002-2004 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Subpeona Documents, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Subpeona Documents (Originals), 2005 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Subpeona Folder - Nancy, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Subpeona Original Documents, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Subpeona Originals - Gale's Search, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Subpeona Originals - Judy's Search, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Subpoena Originals - Secretary's emails and Calendar, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Subpoena Originals - Secretary's emails and Calendar, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Subpoena Originals - Secretary's emails and Calendar, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Substance Abuse Service Council, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Summary of Workshop Issues, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Summary Report on Virginia's Drug Court Program, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Suspension of Passes, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - SVP, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - SVP Budget, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - SWAM Procurement Reports, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Systems Transformation Grant, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Systems Transformation Grant, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - TANF II: Opportunities for a Lifetime - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) Re-authorization Advisory Group, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) Budget, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - REVIEW: Terrorist Threat Protocol, 2003-2004 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Thank yous received, 2002-2005 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Traffic Safety Records Memorandum, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - United Network for Organ Sharing (UNOS)/LifeNet, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - University of Virginia Medical Center: Reprot of Operational Efficiency, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Urban Policy Taskforce, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Value Options: General Information - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - VCU - Bryan Meyer: Structured Decision-Making, undated (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - VCU Health System, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - VDA, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Adult Day Services Association, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Association of Free Clinics, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Board for People with Disabilities - General Information, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Center for Healthy Communities, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Child and Family Services Review: Final Report, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - REVIEW: Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Governmental Frauds Act, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA), 2003-2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA), 2003-2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Medicaid Pharmacy and Therapeutics Committee, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Medicaid Prior Authorization Activities, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Nebraska Alliance, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Poverty Law Center, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Program for All-Inclusive Care for Children and Their Families, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Treatment Center for Children (VTCC), 2005 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Treatment Center for Children, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Treatment Center for Children, undated (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Virginia's Academic Health Centers: Mission-Related Services and Cost, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Virginia's Share of Federal Funds, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - VITA Certification, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Volunteer/Events, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Walk Smart Virginia, 2002-2004 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Walk Smart Virginia, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Web Updated, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Weekly Reports, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Wellness Passport: Nelson, Albemarle and Amherst Counties, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center - Augusta County Water/Sewer, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Work Group on Rural Obstetrical Care: Full Work Group, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Workforce Development Policy, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Workforce Development Policy, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Workforce Development Policy, 2002-2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Workforce Investment Act (WIA), 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Xopenex Medicaid Public Presentation, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- Series IV: Correspondence with State Agencies, 1997-2005 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - Aging: Boards, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Aging: Budget Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Aging: Consituent Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Aging: Decision Memos, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Aging: DOA - Conference on Aging, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Aging: Drug Cards, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Aging: General Information, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Aging: Grants, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Aging: Jefferson Area Board for Aging, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Aging: Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Aging: Personnel Matters, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Aging: Requests for Proclamations, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Aging: Senior Navigator, undated (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Aging: Technology Issues, 2003-2005 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Aging: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Constituent Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Decision Memos, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: General Information, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Legislative Contact, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Mandates, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Rehabilitation Council, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Requests for Proclamations, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Technology Issues, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Blind and Visually Impaired: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Board for People with Disabilities: Boards, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Board for People with Disabilities: Decision Memos, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Board for People with Disabilities: General Information, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Board for People with Disabilities: March 2005 Interim Report, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Board for People with Disabiltiies: Media Issues, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Board for People with Disabilties: Norton Relay Center, undated (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Board for People with Disabilities: Policy Issues, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Comprehensive Services: Board Orientations, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Comprehensive Services: Budget Issues, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Comprehensive Services: Constituent Issues, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Comprehensive Services: Decision Memos, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Comprehensive Services: General Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Comprehensive Services: Hot Button Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Comprehensive Services: Miscellaneous, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Comprehensive Services: Policy Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Comprehensive Services: Public Accounts, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - Comprehensive Services: Steering Committee Letter, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 41)
  - Comprehensive Services: Studies, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 42)
  - Comprehensive Services: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - Council on Indians: General, 2001-2004 (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Decision Memos, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 45)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: General Information, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 46)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Personnel, undated (Box 81, Folder 47)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Report for funding children's hearing aids, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 48)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Technology Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 49)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Virginia Relay, 2002-2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 50)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Virginia Relay, 2002-2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 51)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 52)
  - Health: 2005 Report of the State Child Fatality Review Team, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 53)
  - Health: Abortion, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 54)
  - Health: Birth Certificates, 1997-2003 (Box 81, Folder 55)
  - Health: Boards, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 56)
  - Health: Budget Issues, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 57)
  - Health: Cancer Control Project, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 58)
  - Health: Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 59)
  - Health: Certificate of Public Need (COPN), 2001-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 60)
  - Health: Certificate of Public Need (COPN), 2001-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 61)
  - Health: Certificate of Need (COPN), 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 62)
  - Health: Certificate of Public Need (COPN), 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 63)
  - Health: Compliance Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 82, Folder 1)